I fell asleep, holding a precious jewel in my hand.
The day was warm, with a gentle breeze.
Now, I said, I have nothing to lose.
Then, I woke up and scolded my foolish hand, for the jewel was gone.
All I have left now are memories of an amethyst.
Ui, is the past that important?
Ui said, no matter how small, all her memories were important.
If she lost even one, she'd be sad.
Back then, this hospital room was all we had.
Our own little world.
The only thing keeping us connected to the outside, was Ui's sister, Iroha.
It was all we needed, and we were happy.
Hello, Iroha Tamaki.
I can grant you any wish you desire.
Any wish?
One of these days, we should all go to a theme park.
That reminds me.
They were building one in Daito Ward, but never finished it.
Oh, I know.
Let's come up with a rumor about that place.
Like, it's a happy place where angels hang out.
How about, we call it the rumor of Kilation Land?
Oh, and that play we did that Nemu wrote, could also be a neat rumor.
The rumor of Good Fortune Water.
And that place we had that bad argument?
The friendship-ending staircase.
You're not doing homework now, are you?
Uh-uh, sis.
We're making up urban legends, and we're planting them all over Kamehama.
We thought, if we filled the city with our rumors...
Then, after we died...
Whenever you'd come across one of them, it would get you to remember us.
It's a neat idea.
Can I make one, too?
Sure!
Somewhere in the city, there's a bare Sakura tree.
When the three girls are well again, and are out of the hospital,
they'll go there and, under its branches,
reunite with the girl who always came to visit them.
On that day, the tree will bloom with the prettiest flowers.
And it'll never be bare again.
Now, to invoke it!
This reunion, no matter how long it takes, will make the tree bloom.
And the name of this tree will be...
Rumor of the Eternal Sakura!
Have you thought about my offer from the other day?
It's hard to believe, to be honest.
You humans only believe what you see.
It's such a shame.
Where's Ui?
Ui!
Oh, hi, sis.
Thanks for coming out here so quickly.
I'll rush over any time you need me to.
I am your big sister, after all.
It's good they stabilized you in time.
For a second there, you had me worried.
The doctor said I can't eat the lunches you bring.
Not till I get better, anyway.
You'll be better soon, and then I'll get to stuff you with my lunches.
Bye.
Bye!
Iroha! Did you hear? The doctor said I might get to leave soon!
You should have seen the doctor's faces when they told her.
They couldn't believe it. They said it was like magic.
I guess miracles are real after all.
D.R.I.N.S.
Well, that sucks.
Yeah. What's up? She's been acting kind of weird lately, hasn't she?
She's not coming as often, and when she does, she seems really tired.
It's like Uli's getting better, but now she's getting sick.
Yeah, that shade's definitely the right one.
You look super cute.
It makes me look a little more grown up.
Thanks, sis. I...
Sorry, there's something I have to do.
What could she have to do down here?
What is all this?
This place is unreal.
Where's Iroha?
Oh my gosh! That thing's trying to kill her!
You can save her, if you want.
I can give you the power to save her.
But first, you have to make a contract with me.
A contract?
How's is this place?
I don't know if you have to deal with him.
What should you do with this place?
What's if this is true?
Irohatamaki
If what Kyubei said is the truth, then the reason Irohat became a magical girl was to cure you
But I don't want my sister to suffer because of me
She doesn't deserve that
Maybe if we make a contract with Kyubei and become magical girls too, we can save her
Take it easy, Ui
I don't trust what it told us, so we should proceed with caution
I'm with her
Besides, we don't know anything about magical girls anyway
We should research it
We'll have a better chance of saving your sister if we know what we're dealing with
It won't take us long if we work together, so don't worry
We'll save her
Yeah, together we can do anything
We believed there would be a happy ending
We couldn't have been more naive
Why are you researching witches?
If I can figure out a more efficient way to get rid of them, you know, like all at once
It would make the job easier for magical girls
With that idea in mind, the wishes we picked should be ones that kill witches
Based on what I discovered, witches attack humans, so we should investigate missing person cases in the city
Here's what I found so far
The blue dots are the last location of missing persons
The red dots are where suicides happened
Almost all of them seem to occur in clusters
Yep, and if you add all the disasters and accidents that were likely caused by witches
And then line up the deaths chronologically
The first victim is always a young girl
That means there's a connection between witches appearing and girls disappearing
It's possible the first victims were magical girls who lost to witches
That could explain the amount of mysterious sudden deaths
Next up, let's go talk to an expert on the situation
Okay, I'm here
What did you want to ask me?
Oh, uh, you promised to tell us the truth?
Of course I will
I don't lie
Okay, then, um
What's the reason you do what you do?
Simply put, my goal is to extend the life of the universe
Oh, and how do you do that?
I collect and transform energy, then send it out to the universe
What exactly is a witch anyway?
Negative emotions manifested
What's a soul gem?
The soul of a magical girl
That sounds important
So do you make them?
It's more like I take your energy and give it a physical form
What did my sister pick up in the morgue?
A grief seed
After she picked it up, what did she do with it?
Purified her soul gem
Why?
The more magic you use, the more tainted they become
What happens if you don't purify them?
You won't be able to use your magic properly
Any more questions?
One more, please
If all witches vanished
Would my sister
I mean
Would magical girls
Have normal lives again?
Their fates are intertwined
If there were no more witches
Then there could be no more magical girls either
You see
The only way to get grief seeds
Is to defeat witches
You stupid machine
I'm even more confused now than I was before
We learned a lot though
We know what Cube A's role in all this is
And as for the truth behind magical girls
It's easy to guess that
What is it then?
What is it?
Come on
Guys
These witches
Are what magical girls become
That's what your sister
Will become someday
How do we stop your sister from becoming a witch?
Based on what we now know
Every magical girl is destined to become a witch
And that's the problem
But the solution is simple
We get rid of that destiny
But how do we do that?
I think you haven't been a hundred percent honest with me
What are you talking about?
About magical girls
I heard they become witches
Is that true?
Oh, is that all?
Yes, it's true
Sheesh
I wish you wouldn't waste me like that
All right
Name your wish
And I will grant it
We want power
Power for the sake of the future
And what does that mean?
It's simple, really
We want your power, Cube A
I wish for the power to collect
I wish for the power to transform
I wish for the power to manifest
We're stealing it from you, Cube A
No, you shouldn't
But believe in the future
Some secrets
Do whatever
So
Understand
You shouldn't
Take the power
Shut up
We don't
Not
need
You should
許
You
bures
I
You
Don't
Can't
Give
You
whether
ack
tänker
Oh
Cow
Whew
mac
Mine
Unknown
A
score
Strong
là
Plut
First, we'll use Ui's Collection Power to suck out the impurities from all the Soul Gems.
Next, we'll use my Transformation Power and convert that Gunkit to Magic for Magical Girls to use.
Then, Namlu's Manifestation Power will give that Magic a physical form of energy.
We'll use that energy to expand the range of our automated purification system, which collects and purifies tainted magic.
This efficient system will keep the impurities from building up in Soul Gems forever!
Our plan worked! Naturally!
Ooh, QB's looking kinda empty after losing his powers.
Ui?
Ui! What's wrong? Come on, see something!
Oh no! The impurities are coming in too fast!
Ui, stop the collection process!
I think she's turning into a witch!
No way! We can't let that happen!
Our powers might help reduce the impurities!
The transformation can't keep up!
Ui, come back to us!
Touka, I can't keep up!
You have to!
We can't let her turn no matter what!
It stopped!
No!
It's... it's her soul...
Touka!
It's disintegrating!
I need a vessel to stabilize it!
Ui, I'm sorry!
Ui, I'm sorry...
Whoa!
We did it!
It totally worked!
We succeeded!
Succeeded?
Congratulationi!
I was wondering what made that barrier!
I guess it's yours then?
I'm not a what!
I have a name!
It's Elena Gray!
Magical girls...
Save them!
Ui...
What is up with that witch?
It's not a real one!
It's an artificial witch created from our combined powers!
Huh?
It's just a baby now!
But when it reaches its full maturity...
It'll create a system where magical girls don't become witches!
No it's not!
What are you talking about?
This is still Ui...
Our plan...
Failed!
Huh?
Excuse me, but no, you're wrong!
We didn't fail at all!
And who is this Ui person?
Our friend...
Hey, Elena Gray!
You should totally join up with us!
The revolution would go a lot faster!
Revolutioni would make for an interesting time for sure!
And I'd be perfect for your cause!
What happened?
Why doesn't she remember?
That's it!
After Touka transformed Ui's soul...
I isolated her inside Kyupei...
When I did that...
It must have cut Ui off from this world...
Namu!
We don't have time to stand here listening to you mumble!
There's a ton of magical girls out there to save and by golly we're gonna save them!
Save them?
Yep! All of them!
We have to save my sister!
We have to save her!
Of course!
Our mission to save every magical girl in one swoop!
That a girl!
That's the Nemo I know!
This witch needs a name, so what do you wanna call her?
She's the beginning of hope for magical girls, so...
How about we call her Eve?
Embryo Eve...
We'll free all magical girls from their cycle of despair!
For starters, we're gonna make all the teeny weeny buzzy busybodies disappear for good!
After the revolution, our names will never be forgotten!
El Hora de lo Spetacolo!
Get ready, world!
The liberation of magical girls is coming!
The truth is, we've failed. Things changed for the worse. There's nothing left for us to take back. No one remembers, except me.
Only me.
The truth is, we've failed. Things changed for the worse. There's nothing left for us to take back. No one remembers, except me. Only me.
That's bad!
So again, when we moved, can you make
Go!